

KIM LONG

Data Analyst

Contact information



0947029580





https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100006122359380

Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

Skills

Language::

English

Computer::

MS Office, SQL, R,C++

Objective

Understanding of using MS OFFICE,R, SQL in forecasting, proficient in office computer. I have experience in the field of Statistical Office of District 1 of people committee district 1 company, now I want to accompany my company for a long time in the near future.

Education



Ton Duc Thang University | August 2018 - Sep 2022

Major: Mathematics-Statistic

Work experience



Statistical Office of District 1 | July 2022 - Now

Statistician

- Collect data on the number of employees in the business, the number of hours worked and the base salary
- Direct sampling survey by online and offline survey, analysis and future business evaluation



Hôtel Des Arts SaiGon | July 2022 - Now 2022

Bartender

Main responsibilities:

- Mixing drinks for guests from basic to complex
- Create cocktails, buy and sell alcohol for guests in the room and outside
- track and order wine, food and management



BROLLER | May 2021 - Au 2021

SEO

- -WRITE ARTICLES, GET IDEAS FOR BIKE, TOY CAR FOR CHILDREN
- -WRITING PRODUCT ADVERTISING ARTICLES ON THE MEDIA, SOCIAL NETWORKS